Hey, thanks for meeting me here.
Yeah, no problem. What's going on?
I don't really know how to say this, so I'm just going to say it.
You're starting to scare me. What happened?
I found the letters, David. The ones you hid in your desk.
What? What letters? I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't lie to me! I read every single one of them!
You've been writing to her for months behind my back!
Okay, okay, just calm down. Let me explain.
Explain what? That our entire relationship has been a joke to you?
No! That's not what happened. Just listen to me, please.
Those letters were for my sister. She's been sick, really sick.
Wait... what? Your sister? You told me she moved abroad.
She did. She's in a hospital in London. Stage three. I didn't know how to tell you.
Oh my God. David, I'm so sorry. I had no idea.
I've been pretending everything is fine but it's not. Nothing is fine.
I feel like the worst person alive. I accused you of something horrible.
It's okay. I should have told you from the beginning.
No, it's not okay. I went through your things like some kind of psycho.
Hey, stop. You're not a psycho. You were scared. I get it.
The doctors said if the treatment works, she could be home by summer.
Really? Oh that's wonderful! She's going to make it!
I really hope so. She's the strongest person I know.
We should go visit her. Together. I want to be there for you.
You would do that? After everything that just happened?
Of course I would. That's what love is, you idiot.
Come here. I love you so much.
I love you too. Now let's go book those plane tickets.